I crumbled before your eyes
Hit rock bottom and sunk deeper
To grab onto the last bit of hope
I’ve tried to reach out with both of my hands
Again in this dark place, light up the sky
While looking into your eyes, I’ll kiss you goodbye
Laugh all you want while you still can
Because it’s about to be your turn 1, 2, 3
Ha how you like that?
You gon’ like that that that that that
How you like that?
How you like that that that that that
Now look at you now look at me
Look at you now look at me
How you like that
Now look at you now look at me
Look at you now look at me
How you like that
Your girl need it all and that’s a hundred
10 out of 10 I want what’s mine
Karma come and get some
I feel bad but there’s nothing I can do
Whats up I’m right back
Cock back the trigger
Plain Jane get hijacked
Don’t like me? Then tell me how you like that
In this even darker place shine like the stars
With a smile on my face I’ll kiss you goodbye
Laugh all you want while you still can
Because it’s about to be your turn 1, 2, 3
Ha how you like that?
You gon’ like that that that that that
How you like that?
How you like that that that that that
Now look at you now look at me
Look at you now look at me
How you like that
Now look at you now look at me
Look at you now look at me
How you like that
The day I fell without my wings
Those dark days where I was trapped
You should’ve ended me when you had the chance
Look up in the sky it’s a bird it’s a plane
BLACKPINK!
How you like that
You gon’ like that