After a sweet Hi there’s always a bitter Bye
After every crazy High there’s a Price you have to pay
There’s no answer to this Test I’ll always fall for it Yes
I’m a slave to my emotions
Screw this heartless love
Here I come kick in the door
Give me the strongest one
So obvious, that love
Give me more give me some more
Cling onto the edge of the cliff if you want
With just one word you’re like starstruck again
That warm nervous feeling, extreme excitement
Felt like heaven but you might not get in it
Look at me Look at you who will be in more pain?
You smart like who? You are
If you cry tears of blood from both eyes
So sorry like who? You are
What should I do, I can’t stand myself being so weak
While I force myself to cover my eyes
I need to bring an end to this love
LET’S KILL THIS LOVE
Feelin’ like a sinner
Its so fire with him I go boo hoo
He said you look crazy
Thank you baby
I owe it all to you
Got me all messed up
His love is my favorite
But you plus me sadly can be dangerous
Lucky me Lucky you
After all, in the end we lie
So what so what
If I end up forgetting you
So sorry
I’m not sorry
What should I do, I can’t stand myself being so weak
While I force myself to hide my tears
I need to bring an end to this love
LET’S KILL THIS LOVE
We all commit to love
That makes you cry
We’re all making love
That kills you inside
We must kill this love
Yeah its sad but true
Gotta kill this love
Before it kills you too
Kill this love
Yeah its sad but true
Gotta kill this love