by RentAnAdviser.com
Almost heaven‚ West Virginia
Blue ridge mountains‚ Shenandoah river
Life is old there‚ older than the trees
Younger than the mountains‚ blowing like a breeze
Country roads‚ take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia
Mountain mamma‚ take me home
Country roads
All my memories‚ gather round her
Modest lady‚ stranger to blue water
Dark and dusty‚ painted on the sky
Misty taste of moonshine‚ teardrop in my eye
Country roads‚ take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia
Mountain mamma‚ take me home
Country roads
I hear her voice in the morning hour she calls me
Radio reminds me of my home far away
Driving down the road I get a feeling
That I should have been home yesterday‚ yesterday
Country roads‚ take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia
Mountain mamma‚ take me home
Country roads
Country roads‚ take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia
Mountain mamma‚ take me home
Country roads
Take me home‚ down country roads