aldridge walker and murray for the spurs
that's the way they started memphis when
they took care of the grizzlies although
got
off to a slow start there down for a
nice finish
nice setup from ciaco johnson run off
the line weaves his way to the hole
and scores oh kyle lowry
on the drive murray back out derozan for
a three
oh yes against his old team no less
demar derozan
has decided to join the three-point
parade this season
inside baines flips it up and in not bad
bill
aldridge with the miss the rebound
johnson gets it right back from murray
off the mark rebound lonnie walker
crashing he goes up
and scores too many murray misses after
aldridge spotted him open
van vleet wide open that's got a good
time out there
to a championship last year they won 53
games
inside there's a position to succeed and
you can see the
play design there throwing pascal siacom
in the low block allowing him to go one
on one
johnson is sucked in jacob's man
delivers the ball at exactly the right
moment
going deep and the high archaeaka the
former raptor
comes up with it looking for help it's
derozan 10 on the shot clock
back outside and the jumper oh
new orleans norman powell is known as
the freight train he goes hard to the
basket and there was
duchenne to clean up his mess and
there's now the spurs difference maker
in memphis was the second quarter when
they outscored him 36-20
toronto a little bit different oh look
jacob great effort on the offensive
glass