Every day, in a movie
in a book or in a drama, I feel love
Um- I learn about love
My heart keeps beating as if it’s my own story
Makes my heart pound and swell with hope
Um- I want to know so bad
Ooh Maybe someday
Could it happen to me, too
When will it be? Who will it be?
I wanna know How it could be as sweet as candy
I wanna know How it’s like flying in the sky
I wanna know know know know
What is love? What love feels like
I wanna know How it keeps you smiling all day
I wanna know How the whole world turns beautiful
I wanna know know know know
What is love? Will love come to me someday?
Just imagining all this
Just thinking about it almost makes my heart to burst
Um- How good it feels
If, one day, for real
Love does come to me, I might just cry
Um- I really want to know how it feels
Ooh Maybe someday
Could it happen to me, too
When will it be? Who will it be?
I wanna know How it could be as sweet as candy
I wanna know How it’s like flying in the sky
I wanna know know know know
What is love? What love feels like
I wanna know How it keeps you smiling all day
I wanna know How the whole world turns beautiful
I wanna know know know know
What is love? Will love come to me someday?
Where in the world are you right now
Just when will we get to meet each other
When and how might our relationship start
Don’t know right now, but somehow I feel
that it will be real good
Better than any movie or drama
The greatest love will come, my gut instinct is always right
C’mon, show yourself, I’m all set Ready!
(Wonder where you are) I’m gonna find you
(Wonder where you are) I’m so dying to see you
I can’t take it much longer
How it could be as sweet as candy
How it’s like flying in the sky
I wanna know know know know
What is love? What love feels like
How it keeps you smiling all day
How the whole world turns beautiful
I wanna know know know know
What is love? Will love come to me someday?
I wanna know
I wanna know know know know
What is love?
I wanna know
I wanna know know know know
What is love?
I wanna know